A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Public Safety, 2000-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- Series XI. Speeches, 2002-2005., Extent: .35 cu. ft. (Box 101)
  - Speeches, 2003.
    - Richmond Urban League 89th Annual Scholarship Benefit speech, 2003. (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Special Olympics Torch Run Kick-off Ceremony speech, 2003 May 29. (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Administrative Support Association speech, 2003 November 6. (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Beach Police Department graduation speech, 2003 June 25. (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Emergency Management Conference speech, 2003 March 12. (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Fire Chiefs Association Mid-Atlantic Expo and Symposium speech, 2003 February 21. (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Wendel, Officer Douglas E. memorial service remarks, 2003 August 6. (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Speeches, 2004.
    - "A Celebration of Heroes" speech, 2004 April 14. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Black History Month Program speech, 2004 February 25. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Bon Air Juvenile Correctional Center Service Awards Luncheon speech, 2004 December 14. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Certified Crime Prevention Community Award Ceremony speech, 2004 January 20. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Chesterfield County Fire and EMS graduation speech, 2004 April 2. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - DUI Bill Signing Ceremony speech, 2004 May 27. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - "Emergency Services Day" speech, 2004 July 11. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Governor's KIDSAFE Prevention Conference speech, 2004 November 16. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - GYPSAC Speakout section closing remarks, 2004. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Hampton Regional Criminal Justice Academy graduation speech, 2004 February 20. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Hampton Roads Criminal Justice Academy graduation speech, 2004 February 27. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Hanover Volunteer Firefighter graduation speech, 2004 January 8. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Hazard Mitigation Summit speech, 2004 June 17. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - International Torch Run Conference speech, 2004 November 21. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Kiwanis Club of Richmond speech, 2004 April 19. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - National Association of Blacks in Criminal Justice, Virginia State Conference speech, 2004 March 24. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Probation Officers-Gang Awareness and Intervention Training speech, 2004 September 30. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Protect and Respect Public Safety Institute Kick-off speech, 2004 May 25. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Public Assembly Fire and Life Safety press conference remarks, 2004 February 19. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Send Off Ceremonies for Virginia National Guard 3rd Battalion, 116th Infantry speech, 2004 July 10. (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Fallen Firefighter Service speech, 2004 June 5. (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Fraternal Order of Police Annual Banquet speech, 2004 August 28. (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Hazardous Materials Conference remarks, 2004 September 23. (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Police Officers' Memorial Service remarks, 2004 May 4. (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Public Safety Outreach Conference speech and talking points, 2004 November 17. (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Special Olympics Torch Run Kick-off speech, 2004 May 27. (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Youth Scholarship Banquet, 1st Baptist Church of South Richmond speech, 2004 June 29. (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Speeches, 2005.
    - Bowling, Corporal Jonathan Williams funeral remarks, 2005 February 3. (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - CapWIN/Waynesboro Police Department, 2005 July 22. (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Checkpoint Strikeforce Kick-off remarks, 2005 August 25. (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Chesapeake Police Academy 47th Session speech, 2005 May 18. (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Criminal Justice Services Recogition Awards Ceremony speech, 2005 May 2. (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - "Gang Prevention and Response--A Coordinated Effort" speech, 2005 May 17. (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Governor's Highway Safety Association Conference Awards Luncheon speech, 2005 August 30. (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Governor's Preventing Crime in the Minority Task Force/BBP Roll-out speaking points, 2005 March 22. (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Hampton Drug Court graduation speech, 2005 April 27. (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Hanover County Emergency Communications Officers, National Telecommunications Week graduation speech, 2005 April 11. (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Joint Conference on Juvenile Services speech, 2005 October 17. (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - "Leadership and Ethics" speech, 2005 April 21. (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - National Crime Victims' Week speech, 2005 April 14. (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - "Partnerships and Housing: The Keys to Safer Communities" speech, 2005 April 17. (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Prince William County Police Association Awards Banquet speech, 2005 May 21. (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Protect and Respect Program 1st Biennial Summit Meeting speech, 2005 May 12. (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Public Safety Diversity Fair speech, 2005 July 12. (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Southern Police Institute Alumni Association Conference speech, 2005 July 26. (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Special Olympics Torch Run Kick-off speech, 2005 May 24. (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Administrative Support Association speech, 2005 September 22. (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Mentoring Partnership 3rd Annual Awards Banquet speech, 2005 February 2. (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Police Officers' Memorial Service remarks, 2005 May 3. (Box 101, Folder 11)